mydressupgame.com 2013-05-23

# My Dress Up Game Privacy and Policies

My Dress Up Game Privacy and Ad Policies

**Personal Information**  
http://www.mydressupgame.com is committed to protecting your privacy online. http://www.mydressupgame.com does not collect any personal information. 

**IP address and logging**  
Your IP address is used to gather broad demographic information and to track your general visiting paterns (how many pages you view while at one website, downloads, etc).

**Google Ad Policy**

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve your ads.  
Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the internet.  
Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google advertising privacy policies.

Websites linking to this http://www.mydressupgame.com have chosen to adopt this generic privacy policy as their own. This means that they agree to abide by the principles laid out below.  
**Information that is gathered from visitors**

In common with other websites, log files are stored on the web server saving details such as the visitor's IP address, browser type, referring page and time of visit.

Cookies may be used to remember visitor preferences when interacting with the website.

Where registration is required, the visitor's email and a username will be stored on the server.  
How the Information is used

The information is used to enhance the vistor's experience when using the website to display personalised content and possibly advertising.

E-mail addresses will not be sold, rented or leased to 3rd parties.

E-mail may be sent to inform you of news of our services or offers by us or our affiliates.  
**Opt Out**  
You can opt out most advertisers [here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp). Please note that the nai service will create cookies on your machine as well. 

**Visitor Options**

If you have subscribed to one of our services, you may unsubscribe by following the instructions which are included in e-mail that you receive.

You may be able to block cookies via your browser settings but this may prevent you from access to certain features of the website.  
**Cookies**

Cookies are small digital signature files that are stored by your web browser that allow your preferences to be recorded when visiting the website. Also they may be used to track your return visits to the website.

3rd party advertising companies may also use cookies for tracking purposes.

**Liability**  
It is http://www.mydressupgame.com's policy to respond quickly to claims of intellectual property violation. Upon receiving notification in accordance with any related copyright organization or owner, http://www.mydressupgame.com will immediately disable and remove games in question. 

By using this site, you signify your assent to the My Dress Up Game Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to this Privacy Policy, please do not use this site. We reserve the right to make changes to this Privacy Policy. Please check back from time to time to ensure that you are aware of these changes. Your continued use of this site will signify your acceptance of these changes. 

This document is the sole statement of the Site's Privacy Policy and no summary, restatement or other version thereof, or other privacy statement or policy, in any form, including, without limitation, machine-generated, is valid.
